sitagita.com 2011-05-20

# Privacy - sitagita.com, the largest website for Indian women

[Home](http://sitagita.com/) » Privacy Policy

### **Sitagita.com's Privacy Policy - An Overview**

This privacy statement had been created to demonstrate Sitagita.com's firm commitment to safeguard your privacy. Throughout the website we want to provide you with a safe and secure environment.

**Information Gathering And Usage**

**1\. Registration  
**You may provide us with certain information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address when registering for certain services such as personalisation, chat, e-mail, community pages, contests and promotions. This information will primarily be used for the purpose of providing personalisation and verification.

**2\. Cookies  
**A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Sitagita.com uses cookies for the personalisation feature. Registration: When you register, Sitagita.com uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. If you turn off the cookies in your browser, you may not be able to visit some parts of Sitagita.com. 

**3\. Third Party Advertising  
**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Our third-party advertising companies also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their respective privacy policies. 

**4.Information you Provide  
**When using our site and services, you may provide information about yourself, such as name, address, phone, mobile, and e-mail. This may occur when you register on SitaGita.com. Some of this information may be shown or shared to other users by you or by us.

While you are registered on SitaGita.com you may receive communication from us in any form like email, sms or other mailing or communication models. 

SitaGita.com along with their affiliates and associated sites, hold the complete control on the following items,  
1\. Registration and user accounts  
2\. User database  
3.Feature and product expansions  
4\. Data Sharing

**5\. Data Sharing  
**By using the website and/or registering yourself at SitaGita.com you authorize us & our associate partners to contact you via email or phone call and offer you their services for the product you have opted for, imparting product knowledge, offer promotional offers running on website & offers offered by the associated third parties. And Irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC service, you still authorize us to give you a call from Sitagita.com & associate partners for the above mentioned purposes.

**6\. SMS Communication  
**The website SitaGita.com will send you SMS alerts if you opt for services on our site, even if you are registered on the DNC or DND service, since these are transactional messages important for you in your interaction with the site SitaGita.com and it's services. If you do not wish to receive SMSs from SitaGita.com please send an email to address mentioned at the end of this document.

**7\. Contacting Sitagita.com  
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with Sitagita.com, you can contact:  
sitagita.com - customer support  
sitagita.com Limited  
5 Ambadi Road  
Kotturpuram  
Chennai 600 085  
India  

Email: [customersupport@sitagita.com](mailto:customersupport@sitagita.com)

Post Comment  
---
